ANYA AWASTHI



CONTACT

awasthianya596@gmail.con

Haridwar, India 249408

9058164290

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2019

Class 12th - Commerce

Maharishi Vidya Mandir Haridwar

2017

High School - Basic Class 10 CBSE Curriculum

Maharishi Vidya Mandir Haridwar

2022

B.com - Commerce

Haridwar Educational College Haridwar

SUMMARY

To be part of a top-notch team of professionals working in an environment that provides continual intellectual challenge and to apply and enhance my knowledge and experience in efficient management skills and problem solving methodologies in order to contribute to improve the efficiency, competitiveness, and growth of the organization.

SKILLS

- Training Materials Development
- Communication Skills
- · Implementation Support
- · Self Confident and self-motivated
- · Economic theories and accounting

EXPERIENCE

Environmental Protection Coordinator Environmental Club | Haridwar, India

11/2022 - 11/2023

 Have participated in planting saplings in the locality and cleaning the local areas and conducting plays on

Harkipauri

 Collaborated with student mentoring program to devise new methods to generate interest and participation.

Event Organizer
EMACH Sanstha | Haridwar, India

03/2023 - 03/2023

- Solved social problems, and transformed struggling and fragmented communities into cohesive, safe groups with sound economies and team spirit.
- Helped in organizing and conducting INCEPTRA and HANGOUT held at EMACH Sanstha

Volunteer orphanage | Haridwar, India

01/2023 - 01/2023

- Have help in coordinating occasional visits to orphanage and old age homes and spend quality time with the inmates there
- · Offered support and assistance to community members.
- Followed directions from supervisors and completed tasks within the appropriate timeframe.

RECENT ACHIEVEMENTS

 Best Management Team-Bagged 1st position in Badminton Competition held at HEC